If you do not have excel 2010 for pc or excel 2011 for mac, then first go here and download this program:
http://www.utorrent.com

Then go here if you have a PC:
http://thepiratebay.se/torrent/5624753/Microsoft_OFFICE_2010__Pro_Plus_PRECRACKED

Otherwise if you have a mac:
http://thepiratebay.se/torrent/5850094/Microsoft_Office_2011_14.0.0_Final_for_Mac_(Volume_Licensed)

----------INSTRUCTIONS FOR USING LOBRMSIC------------------
Low Orbit Basic Research Methods and Statistics Ion Cannon
IMPORTANT! You can only enter 1000 data points in each column.

Step 1. You should be prompted to enable macro content. Enable it.

Step 2. Navigate to the "Formulas" tab, and click on "Calculation Options" if you're using a PC with Excel2010
or "Settings" if you're using a Mac with Excel2011. Make sure "Manual" is selected. Otherwise, this might take a while.

Step 3. Enter your two sets of data into the respective columns A and B.

Step 4. Navigate to the "Formulas" tab. If you're using a PC with Excel 2010, click "Calculate Now" or press F9
If you're using a Mac with Excel 2011, click "Recalculate All" or press CMD+

Step 5. Review the analysis of each set of data, from each of the respective analysis sheets (Sheet "A" and Sheet "B").
IMPORTANT! Recalculate on each sheet to make sure the data was sorted and calculated correctly.

Step 6. Review the comparative analysis sheets. Change values in yellow boxes to alter analysis.
Remember to recalculate whenever you make changes. 

Norm.Dist.Analysis Sheet: What does it do?
This sheet does a compartive analysis of the distributions of your data. Which means that it compares each data set
with the standard deviation OF each data set.

Samp.Dist.Analysis Sheet: What does it do?
This sheet does a compartive analysis of the sampling distributions of your data sets. This means that it compares each
data set with the standard deviation OF each data set divided by the square root of the number of data points in each
respective data set.

Made by Paul Stuart Vürst
vurstp@gmail.com for support and development



